Back then, the Eldest Princess supported me as a child emperor
and ruled behind the curtain.
The power in the court was almost entirely in her hands.
Only by acting incompetent and unrestrained could I protect myself
and protect Ayan.
The price was
the fear of the world and a bad reputation.
I have been acting for so many years
that I'm used to it.
But I still don't understand
why you aren't afraid of me.
Why should I be afraid?
Being a tyrant keeps you safe
and lets you act crazy whenever you want.
How great is that?
For instance, when the head female official picked on me,
I beat her up right there.
And she couldn't reason with a crazy person.
How great is that?
Being crazy keeps you safe.
We...
Ayue.
In all your lives,
you must be safe and sound.
Even I
can't hurt you.
Aren't you with Ayue every day?
How do you not know what she likes?
Doesn't Sister Cangyue like your puppy?
Can you give her one?
No.
Puppies aren't toys. I can't give them away.
When will it get dark?
In about four hours.
Xiaoyue, let's go out and play.
Xiaoyue.
One times one is one.
One times two is two.
One times three is three.
Two times three is six.
Two times four is eight.
Three times three is nine.
Your Majesty.
What is it?
Your Majesty is truly handsome.
Jindou, Yuanbao!
Yuanyuan!
Jindou and Yuanbao are missing.
One for you.
One.
A'yan likes Jindou and Yuanbao so much.
Would he really part with them for you?
Of course.
I am his
only brother.
Brother!
Jindou and Yuanbao are missing.
Ah, missing?
Maybe they went out to play.
I don't know.
I'll go with you.
Jindou!
Yuanbao!
Brother, you stole my dog.
You stole my dog.
You stole a child's dog.
I didn't steal his dog.
It was you. You stole my dog.
I don't care.
Go back, go back.
I won't leave.
You stole my dog.
You stole both of the ones you gave me.
All lands belong to the king.
I didn't steal it.
I just took it in the dark.
Look, Pixiu.
Alright.
Don't be sad.
Don't blame your brother either.
He wanted to give me this puppy to play with,
so he accidentally took the wrong one.
Then keep this one, Sister Xiaoyue.
It's fine if it's for you.
Thank you,
Ayan.
Pixiu, let's run.
Do you like it?
You child-stealing dog.
I didn't steal.
Yes, you did.
I really didn't.
The experiencer's character goal is 85% complete.
There is news from General Song.
General Song sent a message saying
that he will arrive in the capital in 2 days.
When General Song arrives,
I will catch him off guard.